(Sheldon:)What a beautiful job Stephanie did.
(Sheldon:)I might have gone
with a mattress suture instead...
(Sheldon:)...but you can't argue with her results.
(Sheldon:)It's a shame it won't scar.
(Sheldon:)The war wound
is a time-honored badge of masculinity.
(Leonard:)I can't remember a time
when you weren't talking.
(Sheldon:)Just for the record, my efforts to establish
you as the alpha male were not aided...
(Sheldon:)- ...by you bursting into tears.
- I did not burst into tears.
(Leonard:)- My eyes just got a little watery.
- Watery?
(Leonard:)She stuck a needle into my hand.
Hey, how's my big crybaby?
(Leonard:)I didn't cry.
(Steph:)Okay, I'm just teasing you.
(Steph:)But, yeah, you did.
(Steph:)It's all good. What do you say
we get you home, put you to bed?
Oh. Are you still gonna spend the night?
(Steph:)Uh, no. I think that you
probably need to rest.
(Sheldon:)She's right. As long as you're vomiting,
coitus is contraindicated.